Presenter: OK. It begins with B.
It’s an adjective for a man who has no hair on his head!
Victoria: Bald.
Presenter: Right.
It begins with C.
It’s an adjective.
It describes a place where there are a lot of people,
for example a restaurant or a beach in the summer.
Victoria: Crowded.
Presenter: Right.
It begins with G.
They’re things which people wear on their hands.
Victoria: Gloves.
Presenter: Right.
It begins with K.
It’s the room where people cook.
Victoria: Kitchen.
Presenter: Right.
It begins with L.
It’s an adjective for someone who doesn’t like studying or working, for example.
It’s the opposite of hard-working.
Victoria: Lazy.
Presenter: Right.
It begins with T.
It’s a thing which you use in an airport to help you with your cases,
or in a supermarket to put your shopping in…
Just three seconds left…
Victoria: Trolley!
Presenter: Congratulations, Victoria! You’ve done it!
Victoria: Oh, great!